Finding Aid for Charles Fey papers, 1914-1970
Bentley Historical Library, University of Michigan
- Other research and personal interests
  - Royal Oak and Oakland County, Michigan
    - Oakland County, Michigan history 1955, 1961-1962, 2 folders (Box 9)
      (folders 316-317)
    - Sherman Stevens, correspondence about 1953-1955, 4 folders (Box 9)
      (folders 318-321)
    - Royal Oak history, clippings (Box 9)
      (folder 322)
  - Chicago Pneumatic Tool Company history
    - Correspondence 1951-1962, 13 folders (Box 9)
      (folders 323-335)
    - Miscellanea, 4 folders (Box 9)
      (folders 336-339)
  - Townsite Community Congregational Church
    - Miscellanea, 4 folders (Box 9)
      (folders 340-343)
  - Royal Oak Township history, 5 folders (Box 9)
    (folders 344-348)